http://www.badmintonindia.org/organization/policy/

Last Updated:
Selection Procedure
Member Selection»
Junior
Senior
BAI Magazine»
Election Procedure
Regulations»
BAI Disciplinary Regulations
BWF Tournament Regulations»
BWF - Code of Conduct For Coaches/Team/TO
Letter - LAWS OF BADMINTON – CHANGES & ADDITIONS TO LAWS & REGULATIONS
Player's Guide-Instant Review System
BWF - Guidelines for Players
BWF - Offences and Penalities
BWF - Players Code of Conduct
Updated BWF Regulations - Amendments to the Code of Conduct in Relation to Betting, Wagering and Irregular Match Results (General Competition Regulations – Appendix 5)
COMPITITION REGULATIONS & MAJOR CHANGES IN BAI DOMESTIC TOURNAMENTS DURING THE YEAR 2016-2017
Affiliated Organizations
Balance Sheet»
FY 2017-18
FY 2016-17
FY 2015-16
History
News
News & Updates
Global Headlines
Press Releases
Events
ACTC - Annual Calender for Training and Competition»
Details of International Competition Organised in India
List of Core Group
National Coaching Camp
Participation in International Event - Seniors
Participation in International Event - Juniors
BAI Calendar
BAC Calendar
BWF Calendar
Players
Players Notices»
SAI - AGE ESTIMATION TEST
AGE FRAUD NOTICE
Change of Address for Issuing New BAI Player ID
BWF ID Form
BAI-ID of Players
BWF-ID of Indian Players
BAI Ranking of Players
Players Profile»
Men's Singles
Men's Doubles
Women's Singles
Women's Doubles
Mix Doubles
Procedure for Acquiring BAI-ID
Awardees»
Arjuna Award
Dronacharya Award
Padma Awards
Rajiv Gandhi Khel Ratna Award
BWF - Meritorious Service Award
BWF - Certificate of Commendation Award
Sharma Award
George Lewis Cup
National Winner»
List of National Championship Winners since 1934
National Winners
All England Badminton Champions (India)
RTI
Photos
Videos
Para Badminton
Anti Doping
World Anti-doping Agency (WADA)
WADA Education and Awareness
Prohibited List and Methods 2018 (WADA)
ADAMS and Whereabouts
BWF Anti-Doping Regulations
Contact Us
Search Results:
Close
BadmintonIndia>organization>policy
Organization
Overview
President's Letter
Mission and Vision
Constitution
Structure
BAI Tournament Regulations
Disciplinary Regulations (under revision)
History
Copyright
Terms of Use
Privacy Policy
PRIVACY POLICY
At the Badminton Association of India ("BAI") we are committed to respecting the privacy rights of our customers and all visitors to our website.
Your privacy is important to us and we aim for our website to be a safe and enjoyable environment for our audience. We respect and safeguard the personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") we receive and collect from you on our website and in the course of our other interactions online.
This Privacy Policy ("Privacy Policy") explains:
what information we may collect about you online;
the use and role of cookies and similar technologies on our website;
how we will protect and use information we collect about and from you;
the circumstances in which we might disclose your details to anyone else;
when we may use your details to contact you; and
how you can be sure the information we hold about you is accurate and current.
Information Gathered
In general, you can visit our website without revealing your identity or any Personal Information about yourself. However, you may not be able to access certain areas or services that require registration or need you to reveal your identity and/or other information about you.
Information that we collect from you will vary depending upon the activity you seek to engage in and may include your name, email address, phone number, mobile number, home address, date of birth, and credit card information. In addition, we may collect demographic information such as gender, information about your computer, hardware, software, platform, media, Internet Protocol (IP) address and connection, information about online activity such as feature usage and click paths, and other data that you may provide in surveys or online profiles. We may combine demographic information with Personal Information to tailor our offerings or web pages to your preferences or interests.
Personal Information
Personal Information means any information that may be used to identify you and that is not otherwise publicly available, including, but not limited to, your first and last name, home or other physical address and an email address, phone number or other contact information.
We may collect Personal Information from you when you register for any of our services or otherwise voluntarily provide such information. If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter(s) and other marketing materials, we will use your name and email address to send the newsletter and materials to you.
Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies
Some of our web pages may also utilise "cookies" and other tracking technologies. A "cookie" is a small text file that may be used, for example, to collect information about your activity on our website. Some cookies and other technologies may serve to recall Personal Information previously indicated by you. Most browsers allow you to control cookies, including whether or not to accept them and how to remove them. You may set most browsers to notify you if you receive a cookie, or you may choose to block cookies with your browser, but please note that if you choose to erase or block your cookies, you may need to re-enter your original user ID and password to gain access to certain parts of our website.
Tracking technologies may automatically record information such as Internet domain and host names; other information about your geographic location; IP addresses; browser software and operating system types; CPU type; your manner of connecting to the Internet (e.g., connection speed through narrowband or broadband access); click paths; and dates and times that our website is accessed.
Our use of cookies and other tracking technologies allows us to improve our website and consequently your web experience. We may also analyse information that does not include Personal Information for trends and statistics.
Children
Our services and our website are intended for a general audience. The products or services offered on our website are not intended for purchase directly by children. If you are a child under the age of 18 and desire to use this website or purchase our products or use our services, please request your parent to register with us and to complete the transaction. Any use of this website or any of its features by a child under the age of 18 must be with parental supervision. We do not contact children under the age of 18 about special offers or for marketing purposes without a parent's permission. We do not ask a child under age of 18 for more Personal Information, as a condition of participation, than is reasonably necessary to participate in a given activity on our website.
Uses of Personal Information
We may use Personal Information and other information received and collected from you to provide the services you have requested, including services that display customised content and to contact you upon your request and when otherwise necessary. We may also use Personal Information for auditing, research and analysis, and to operate and improve our services. In certain circumstances, we may share aggregated non-personal information with third parties. When we use third parties to assist us in processing your Personal Information, we require that they comply with our Privacy.
Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures. We may also share such information with third parties in limited circumstances, including when complying with legal process, preventing fraud or imminent harm, and ensuring the security of our network and services.
Where we propose to use your Personal Information for any other uses we will ensure that we notify you first. You will also be given the opportunity to withhold or withdraw your consent for your use other than as listed above.
Confidentiality and Security
We will keep confidential and protect your Personal Information except where disclosure is required or permitted by law.
We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the Personal Information submitted to us, both during transmission and, once we receive it, for storage and disposal. When you enter sensitive information on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). All information we gather is securely stored within databases controlled by us. The databases are stored on servers secured behind a firewall; access to the servers is password-protected and is strictly limited. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
We limit access to Personal Information to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.
Third parties provide certain services available on our website and on our behalf. We may provide information, including Personal Information, to third-party service providers to help us deliver our products, information, and services efficiently and effectively. Service providers are also an important means by which we maintain our website and mailing lists. We will take reasonable steps to ensure that these third-party service providers are obligated to protect Personal Information on our behalf through confidentiality agreements and otherwise. We do not intend to transfer Personal Information without your consent to third parties who are not bound to act on our behalf unless such transfer is legally required. Similarly, it is against our policy to sell Personal Information collected online without consent.
If you choose to provide us with your Personal Information, we may transfer that Personal Information from your country or jurisdiction to other countries or jurisdictions around the world. Your Personal Information may be collected and stored on servers located in the territory of India and such other countries as we may disclose from time to time.
Third Party Websites
If you click on a link to a third party site or otherwise leave the BAI website you will go to a website that is outside the purview of our control. Because we cannot control the activities of third parties, we cannot accept responsibility for any use of your Personal Information by such third parties, and we cannot guarantee that they will adhere to the same privacy and security practices as we do. The use of Personal Information by such websites shall be governed by the privacy policies provided therein. Therefore, if you visit a third party website that is linked to our website, you should consult that website's privacy policy before providing any Personal Information.
Contacting You
We may contact you using the Personal Information you have given us:
in relation to the functioning of any service you have signed up for in order to ensure that we can deliver the services to you;
where you have opted to receive further correspondence;
to invite you to participate in surveys about the our services (participation is always voluntary); and
to provide you information about our new products and services, where you have specifically agreed to receive this.
Change of Control
In the event that ownership or control of the BAI was to change, your Personal Information may be transferred. If such a transfer results in a material change in the use of your Personal Information, the BAI will provide notice about the choices you have to decline to permit such a transfer.
Accuracy
To the extent that you do provide us with Personal Information, we wish to maintain accurate and current Personal Information. Where we collect Personal Information from you on our website, should you need to update or correct that Personal Information, please contact us and we will make reasonable efforts to incorporate the changes in your Personal Information that we hold as soon as practicable.
Consent; Amendments; Law
By using this website, you consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy and to our use and management of Personal Information for the purposes and in the manner herein provided. Should this Privacy Policy change, we intend to take every reasonable step to ensure that these changes are brought to your attention by posting all changes prominently on our website for a reasonable period of time.
Your visit and any dispute over privacy are subject to this Privacy Policy. The said Policy shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the Republic of India. Further, it is irrevocably and unconditionally agreed that the courts of New Delhi, India shall have exclusive jurisdiction to entertain any proceedings in relation to any disputes arising out of the same.
Contact Us
Communication Addresses
BAI Head Office,
Badminton Association of India,
D-6/10, Vasant Vihar,New Delhi - 110 057
(INDIA)
Tel: +91-11-41450524 (O)
SH. AJAY KUMAR SINGHANIA,
Badminton Association of India,
D-6/10, Vasant Vihar,New Delhi - 110 057
(INDIA)
Tel:      +91-11-41450525 (O)
Email: ajaysinghania003@gmail.com
Dr. ANBUMANI RAMADOSS
MEMBER OF PARLIAMENT,
HONY. TREASURER
10 THILAK STREET, T NAGAR,
CHENNAI- 600017
Email: presidenttnba@gmail.com
Disclaimer: The BAI Web Site contains information and material compiled for reference only.
Information on this web site is provided solely for the user’s information and, while due
care has been taken to make it accurate, it is provided without guarantee of any kind,
either expressed or implied. BAI will not be liable for any legal action/ damages, direct
or indirect, arising from the use of this web site. BAI reserves the right to make changes
in this material at any time without notice.
VISITORS
BAI Megazine
©2013 Badminton Association of India | All Rights Reserved |
Page generated in 0.0245 seconds.
| Website designed and developed by MelonSys Solutions
